telugunow.com 2014-02-12

# Privacy Policy, TeluguNow.com - Privacy policy, Privacy Statement,

##  TeluguNow.com – Privacy Policy , Terms and conditions of usage

TeluguNow.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

 **INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY LOGGED**

We might use your IP address only to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as where in the world our visitors are based or the names of companies that visit the site.

 **ADVERTISERS**

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

 **SURVEYS**

Any online surveys ask visitors for demographic information, such as location, age, employer etc. They will also ask specific questions about your use ands interest in the site. Any contact information will never be disclosed out side the company or used by TeluguNow.com for marketing reasons.

 **E-MAIL’S**

TeluguNow.com may record e-mail addresses on a file supplied to us by visitors. We will never let outside companies have access to this database.

This site contains links to other sites.TeluguNow.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **SECURITY**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

 **NEWS**

News Articles published in TeluguNow is collected from different sources. TeluguNow is not responsible for the correctness of the news.

News articles are presented sololy for sharing the information to our visitors. We do not hold any copyrights.

To request removal of any article from this site with proofs, Please write to : admin(@)TeluguNow.com and allow us to remove your articles which needs sufficient time.

 **Contacting the Web Site:**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us by just sending us an E-Mail : admin(@)TeluguNow.com.

 **All rights reserved:** Reproduction of this website, in whole or in part, in any form or medium without express written permission from TeluguNow.com is prohibited.

 **Disclaimer:** Information furnished in this site is collected from various sites or resources. Content copy rights are rested with respective authors.

 **GD Star Rating**  
 _a WordPress rating system_

Privacy Policy, 5.0 out of 5 based on 1 rating 

### Comments

comments
